mlspropertyfinder.com 2019-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Elevate | Elm Street Technology - Lead generation, nurturing & follow-up - Social Media Marketing for Real Estate Agents - Responsive Real Estate Websites - IDX Integration

This website is owned and operated by Elm Street Technology, LLC either directly or through one of its affiliates (individually and collectively hereinafter referred to as “Elm Street”). Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Elm Street, we want to make your experience online both satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

## Information collected and tracked by Elm Street

In general, when you visit our website, you remain anonymous.

### Optional Voluntary Information

There are occasions where we may ask you to voluntarily submit additional information about yourself, such as your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address. We may also request your credit card number and expiration date. We may request this information to register you as an account holder, manage your account, be able to better understand your needs, adjust our website to your personal preferences, enable you to order products and services via the website, enable you to participate in any message boards, and send you e-mail and postal mail newsletters and announcements, and for other similar business purposes. We give you the opportunity to elect not to receive future materials from us.

### Usage Tracking

We collect tracking information and monitor traffic patterns throughout this website; however, we do not correlate this information with data about individual users unless you are a registered account holder. We do break down overall usage statistics according to a user’s domain name, browser type, and MIME type by reading this information from the browser string (information contained in every user’s browser. This information allows us to better tailor our content to users’ needs and to help our advertisers and sponsors better understand the demographics of our audience.

### Other Data Collection

We may collect data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this policy. For example, you might contact us with a question. We maintain such data like other business records. All opinions, ideas, suggestions, and other feedback submitted through our website may be used by Elm Street, without any restriction and free of charge, and nothing contained in this policy shall limit or otherwise affect this.

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information such as the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the website from which you linked into our website or an advertisement.

Please note that Elm Street will fully cooperate with any court order or other legal process and will provide your personal information to the extent required in any legal proceeding.

### Use of information and protection of your privacy

As mentioned above, Elm Street may use personal information about you and track your usage of our website to register you as an account holder, manage your account, be able to better understand your needs, adjust our website to your personal preferences, enable you to use the services provided by the website, order products and services via the website, enable you to participate in any message boards, and send you e-mail and postal mail newsletters and announcements, and for other similar business purposes. Elm Street does not disclose its mailing lists to any outside parties. Also, we will not share your personal information with any outside parties without your permission, unless such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.

We may use third party contractors who can access our databases for the purpose of conducting repairs or upgrades to our computer system. We may also use third party service providers and give access to your personal information as part of the services they provide to us. We hold all such third parties to the same privacy standards to which we hold ourselves. We require these third parties to use and disclose your personal information only as necessary to perform their services.

### Children

Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), Elm Street will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If we discover that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with any personally identifiable information, we will delete that information from our systems.

### Cookies

Elm Street may place text files called "cookies" in the browser files of your computer. The cookies themselves do not contain personal information, although they will enable us to relate your use of this website to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information cookies can contain is information you supply yourself. Cookies can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Elm Street uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). We may also use cookies when you register for an account. In these situations, a cookie will store useful information that enables our website to remember you when you return to visit us.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you do need cookies to participate actively in the message boards and forums. Please refer to your browser instructions for information regarding erasing, blocking, and receiving warnings for cookies.

### Security

Elm Street operates secure data networks protected by industry standard security protocols, such as (if and where appropriate) firewalls, encryption, and password protection systems. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized individuals have access to the information provided by our users.

### Unsubscribe / Opt-out Policy

You may unsubscribe or opt-out of receiving electronic correspondence from us by either logging into your account to modify your preferences or following any instructions in such electronic correspondence on how to unsubscribe or opt-out from that list. The foregoing does NOT opt you out of receiving e-mail correspondence about your account.

### Links

This website may contain links to other websites that are not under our control. Elm Street is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites, and we provide the links solely for the convenience and information of our visitors.

### Your consent

By using this website, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Elm Street. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.

### Contact us

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us: Elm Street, LLC, P.O. Box 10768, Greensboro, North Carolina 27404, 336-353-3456, support@listingbook.com.
